{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072862359","data":{"timestamp":" 947072862359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_30","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072876269","data":{"timestamp":" 947072876269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072897136","data":{"timestamp":" 947072897136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitezu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITEZU"," userResponse":" VITEZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072902742","data":{"timestamp":" 947072902742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vitezu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITEZU"," userResponse":" VITEZU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072904309","data":{"timestamp":" 947072904309"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mozagu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAGU"," userResponse":" MOZAGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072907578","data":{"timestamp":" 947072907577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mozagu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAGU"," userResponse":" MOZAGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072909157","data":{"timestamp":" 947072909157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dopufa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOPUFA"," userResponse":" DOPUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072911734","data":{"timestamp":" 947072911734"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dopufa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOPUFA"," userResponse":" DOPUFA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072913307","data":{"timestamp":" 947072913307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sovipa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOVIPA"," userResponse":" SOVIPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072916075","data":{"timestamp":" 947072916075"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sovipa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SOVIPA"," userResponse":" START_SOVIPA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072919164","data":{"timestamp":" 947072919164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" sovipa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SOVIPA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072920738","data":{"timestamp":" 947072920738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vomuzo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VOMUZO"," userResponse":" VOMUZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072923594","data":{"timestamp":" 947072923594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" vomuzo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VOMUZO"," userResponse":" VOMUZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072925160","data":{"timestamp":" 947072925160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tafemi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFEMI"," userResponse":" TAFEMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072927924","data":{"timestamp":" 947072927923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tafemi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFEMI"," userResponse":" TAFEMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072929496","data":{"timestamp":" 947072929496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fihulu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIHULU"," userResponse":" FIHULU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072931900","data":{"timestamp":" 947072931900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fihulu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIHULU"," userResponse":" FIHULU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072933475","data":{"timestamp":" 947072933475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tuvari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUVARI"," userResponse":" TUVARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072935945","data":{"timestamp":" 947072935945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tuvari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUVARI"," userResponse":" TUVARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072937505","data":{"timestamp":" 947072937505"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jezipi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEZIPI"," userResponse":" JEZIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072940262","data":{"timestamp":" 947072940262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jezipi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEZIPI"," userResponse":" JEZIPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072941838","data":{"timestamp":" 947072941838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hufuvo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFUVO"," userResponse":" HUFUVO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072944404","data":{"timestamp":" 947072944404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hufuvo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFUVO"," userResponse":" HUFUVO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::nonwrd.len-6.rand.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072946418","data":{"timestamp":" 947072946418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" hufuvo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072946504","data":{"timestamp":" 947072946504"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" 8e094ce7-7869-4948-b030-9ffda94875cd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__nonwrd.len-6.rand.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hufuvo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUFUVO"," userResponse":" HUFUVO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072970966","data":{"timestamp":" 947072970966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_rutiza_fihulu-mozagu-rutiza"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" rutiza"," userResponse":" rutiza"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072978083","data":{"timestamp":" 947072978083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ponuvi_fekewa-rinoke-ponuvi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ponuvi"," userResponse":" ponuvi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072984082","data":{"timestamp":" 947072984082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_lorewi_jezipi-lorewi-bodabi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" lorewi"," userResponse":" lorewi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072990421","data":{"timestamp":" 947072990421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_tafemi_tafemi-rutiza-sovipa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tafemi"," userResponse":" tafemi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947072997946","data":{"timestamp":" 947072997946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sujuye_vitezu-sujuye-jowoma"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sujuye"," userResponse":" sujuye"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073005555","data":{"timestamp":" 947073005555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_fihulu_peyake-hufuvo-fihulu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" fihulu"," userResponse":" fihulu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073013992","data":{"timestamp":" 947073013992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_vomuzo_bodabi-vomuzo-zojuwu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vomuzo"," userResponse":" vomuzo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073023749","data":{"timestamp":" 947073023749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_walimu_lununa-walimu-yulefo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" walimu"," userResponse":" walimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073030047","data":{"timestamp":" 947073030047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_yenake_yenake-zojuwu-veweho"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" yenake"," userResponse":" yenake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073043639","data":{"timestamp":" 947073043639"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sovipa_hufuvo-sujuye-sovipa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sovipa"," userResponse":" sovipa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947073049422","data":{"timestamp":" 947073049422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_144723"," gameId":" af356e8e-93c3-4fde-9b98-e1d6648ad6dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_nonwrd.6.lc.rand.stat.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_sovipa_hufuvo-sujuye-sovipa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}